{
    "subject": "resource/Eugenio_Mar\u00eda_de_Hostos",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos (January 11, 1839 \u2013 August 11, 1903), known as \"El Gran Ciudadano de las Am\u00e9ricas\" (\"The Great Citizen of the Americas\"), was a Puerto Rican educator, philosopher, intellectual, lawyer, sociologist, and Puerto Rican independence advocate.",
    "human_readable": "Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Puerto Rican educator, philosopher, intellectual, lawyer, sociologist, and Puerto Rican independence advocate.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9728310108184814,
            "question": "In what ways did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos advocate for Puerto Rican independence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9682194590568542,
            "question": "Was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos involved in the Puerto Rican independence movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8896138668060303,
            "question": "What was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.880714476108551,
            "question": "What is the significance of Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos's contributions to Puerto Rico?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8480246663093567,
            "question": "What subjects did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos likely teach as an educator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7803893685340881,
            "question": "What nationality was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6442149877548218,
            "question": "Can you name some key ideas or beliefs that Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos promoted?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6373674869537354,
            "question": "What role did philosophy play in Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5904603600502014,
            "question": "Besides education, what other fields did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos contribute to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4329749047756195,
            "question": "How would you describe Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos's multifaceted career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Puerto Rican educator, philosopher, intellectual, lawyer, sociologist, and Puerto Rican independence advocate.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5858_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides education, what other fields did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos contribute to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5858_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did philosophy play in Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5858_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name some key ideas or beliefs that Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos promoted?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5858_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5858_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide multiple sources that confirm Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Puerto Rican educator, philosopher, intellectual, lawyer, sociologist, and Puerto Rican independence advocate. For example:\n\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5858/re-ranker-msmarco/72.txt\n  mentions \"He is revered throughout the Americas, including the U.S.\" as a educator, philosopher, intellectual, lawyer, sociologist, novelist, and Puerto Rican independence advocate.\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5858/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt\n  mentions \"It is as statue of Eugenio Maria de Hostos who is a famous Puerto Rico educator, philosopher, intellectual, lawyer, sociologist and independence advocate.\"\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5858/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt\n  mentions \"Hostos attended school in Mayag\u00fcez and San Juan and studied law in Spain\"\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5858/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt\n  provides a detailed description of Hostos' roles as \"A Puerto Rican educator, writer and patriot\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos stating that he was an educator, philosopher, intellectual, lawyer, sociologist, and a Puerto Rican independence advocate. Therefore, the statement \"Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Puerto Rican educator, philosopher, intellectual, lawyer, sociologist, and Puerto Rican independence advocate\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}